Guide to the United Campus Christian Fellowship Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Campus Christian Fellowship Records
1953-1969
RG 254
Yale University Divinity School Library
3.3
(8 boxes)
The United Campus Christian Fellowship was a national, Protestant, ecumenical organization that existed between the years 1960-1968.
United Campus Christian Fellowship
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Princeton Theological Library
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The United Campus Christian Fellowship was a national, Protestant, ecumenical student movement that existed between 1960-1968. The UCCF was a merger between the student work departments of the Disciples of Christ, the Presbyterian Church in U.S.A., Evangelical United Brethren, and the United Church of Christ. Once merged, the UCCF was comprised of regional member movements and local groups. UCCF was also a participating member of the National Student Christian Federation and later the University Christian Movement. In 1968, the UCCF voted to dissolve as the UCM had taken its place as the national Christian student movement.
Scope and Contents
Files include correspondence, reports, and publications of regional UCCF groups and related organizations.
Arrangement
I. UCCF Regional Organizations
II. Related Organizations and Projects
Universities and colleges -- Religion; Youth in the ecumenical movement
- UCCF Regional Organizations, Series I
  - Arizona, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - N. California, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - S. California, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Southern California Region, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - South California, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Colo-Wyoming, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Illinois, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Indiana, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Iowa, 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kansas Region, 1961-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - K.I.M.O.N.A (Kansas, Iowa, Missouri, Oklahoma, Nebraska, Arkansas), 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kentucky, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Michigan, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Michigan (cont'd), 1961-1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Minnesota, N.D., S.D, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Missouri, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Missouri, 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Miss, Ala, Ga, Fla., 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Nebraska, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - New England, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - New England, 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - New England, 1961-1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - New England (cont'd), 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - New Jersey, Pennsylvania, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - New Mexico, SW Texas, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - New York, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New York (cont'd), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - North Carolina, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Ohio, 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Ohio, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ohio, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Oklahoma, Arkansas, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Pacific Central, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Pennsylvania, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Tennessee, 1963-1966 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Texas, Louisiana, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Utah, S. Idaho, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - West Virginia, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Virginia, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Pacific Northwest - Wash, Oregon, Montana, N. Idaho, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Wisconsin, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Related Organizations and Projects, Series II
  - Afro-Asian Seminar, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Afro-Asian Seminar, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Southern Africa Study Movement, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - East Asia Seminar, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Middle East Study Seminar, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Frontier Internships, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - MSM (Methodist Student Movement), 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - MSM (cont'd), 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - MSM, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - MSM (cont'd), 1960-67 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Methodist Student Movement - MSM, 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - University Christian Movement Misc Folder -Richard Van Voorhis file -Publication Secretary -Mostly Field Dept related 1966 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - UCM 66-67 -Misc File -Richard Van Voorhis UCM File -Separated printed materials from corresp., 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - UCM 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - UCM Assemby 1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - UCM Gen. Comm. 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Brochures, 1953-1964 (Box 8, Folder 59)